<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><listings><listing><record_id>17</record_id><title><![CDATA[9544 Sierra Vista Ct NE, Albuquerque, NM]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://localhost/flyerme/showflyer.aspx?oid=17]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Apartment/Condo/Townhouse]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://localhost/flyerme/order/17/photo1/65DA829FD8DEBA2FB341992A037200A7_Photo1.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[9544 Sierra Vista Ct NE]]></address><city><![CDATA[Albuquerque]]></city><state><![CDATA[NM]]></state><zip><![CDATA[87111]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>0</bedrooms><bathrooms>0</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1069]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[0]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[0]]></parking_spots><year_built>1983</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>159999</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Central heat, Fireplace, High/Vaulted ceiling, Walk-in closet, Hardwood floor, Tile floor, Family room, Living room, Bonus/Rec room, Office/Den, Dining room, Breakfast nook, Dishwasher, Refrigerator, Attic, Granite countertop, Microwave, Stainless steel appliances, Stove/Oven, Basement, Washer, Dryer, Laundry area - inside, Laundry area - garage, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Yard, Swimming pool, Jacuzzi/ Whirlpool, Sauna]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Sat, 16 Apr 2016 01:51:08 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100028</record_id><title><![CDATA[7159 Ridge Ave, Coopersburg, PA]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=28]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/gregreph/Thumbs100_ridge brighter right frnt angle.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[7159 Ridge Ave]]></address><city><![CDATA[Coopersburg]]></city><state><![CDATA[PA]]></state><zip><![CDATA[18036]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[4230]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[43917]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2000</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>523000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Basement, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Microwave, Yard, Family room, Swimming pool, Living room, Jacuzzi/Whirlpool, Bonus/Rec room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Stunning home with 3 full finished levels of 4230 sq feet.  Extensive windows, expansive views, huge eat inkit with island, serving bar and more.  Large formal dining room, super master bedroom suite, 3 full plus 2 half baths, inground pool, deck, patio, covered front porch.
Beautiful home in top location.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 12 Jan 2009 15:48:53 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100043</record_id><title><![CDATA[34505 Dogwood Lane, Alta, CA]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=43]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/le.breeze/Thumbs100_MLS PHOTOS001.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[34505 Dogwood Lane]]></address><city><![CDATA[Alta]]></city><state><![CDATA[CA]]></state><zip><![CDATA[95701]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[2811]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[2.5]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2001</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>498900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Basement, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Yard, Granite countertop, Living room, Stainless steel appliances, Bonus/Rec room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[EXCEPTIONAL 2800+ SF HOME ON 2.5 ACRES LOCATED IN THE QUAINT MOUNTAIN COMMUNITY OF ALTA. Designed to be low maintenance and energy efficient, this home will save time and money. Perfect for retirement living or the home business professional. The 3 bedroom, 3 full bathroom home is situated on a heavily treed parcel with fragrant dogwood, oak, pine, fir and cedar. Beautiful low maintenance gardens with mature azalea, rhododendrons, perennials and winding paved paths surround the front of the home. The striking interior double leaded glass doors lead to a open floor plan, with living room, dining room, kitchen, guest room/office and master suite all on the main level. A family room loft with rustic wood vaulted ceilings and a cozy woodstove, a lower level private third bedroom and a laundry room complete the floor plan. The kitchen has recently been remodeled with beautiful granite countertops, a travertine backsplash and top of the line stainless steel appliances. It also has plentiful storage cabinets and a walk in pantry. The dining and living rooms are large and perfect for family gatherings. The master bedroom feels like a luxury hotel suite due to its large size and spa like bathroom. A comfy sitting area with fireplace will keep you warm. Double French doors lead to the private rear deck with serene forest views. Energy efficient features include individually controlled zoned heating in each room, quality Hunter ceiling fans throughout, dual paned windows, energy efficient appliances, on demand water heating system, and two Mendota fireplaces. A huge basement area can be used for storage or workspace. The oversized 2 car garage can double as a workshop as it is equipped with 220 electrical and compressed airlines. The home has high-speed internet and satellite TV access. Low maintenance features include porcelain tile, laminate flooring, powder coated deck railings and entry gate, natural landscaping with automatic sprinklers, fiberglass exterior doors, Trex-type decking, metal roofing and city water with all new lines to main. The exterior also has a garden shed, raised garden beds, an indoor/outdoor dog run, and wildlife feeding areas, so that you can enjoy the outdoors.  A large level area is fenced and paved for privacy, with plenty of parking. Perimeter lighting highlights the beautiful property in the evening. This lovingly cared for home is ready to enjoy all the benefits of mountain living. Must see to appreciate the quality!]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Sat, 28 Feb 2009 14:09:42 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100083</record_id><title><![CDATA[1512 Williamsburg Road, Richmond, VA]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=83]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/ernie/Thumbs100_1512 Williamsburg Rd.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[1512 Williamsburg Road]]></address><city><![CDATA[Richmond]]></city><state><![CDATA[VA]]></state><zip><![CDATA[23231]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>1</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1458]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[4165]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1930</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>91500</price><amenities><![CDATA[Dining room, Laundry area - inside, Hardwood floor, Tile floor, Yard, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Great investment property opportunity! Either fix up and rent or fix up and flip!]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 22 Jun 2009 11:23:23 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100090</record_id><title><![CDATA[15209 SE 80th St., Newcastle, WA]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=90]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/George.thurtle/Thumbs100_2 dining.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[15209 SE 80th St.]]></address><city><![CDATA[Newcastle]]></city><state><![CDATA[WA]]></state><zip><![CDATA[98059]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>5</bedrooms><bathrooms>5</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[6059]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[12790]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2006</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>1599000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Microwave, Yard, Family room, Granite countertop, Swimming pool, Living room, Stainless steel appliances, Jacuzzi/Whirlpool, Bonus/Rec room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Tremendous value on this Johnson Design Model Home. True luxury custom qaulity with onsite stained millwork throughout, venetian plaster wall accents, terrazo floors on main level with heat pads, security system with video cameras and remote viewing. Not a short sale or bank owned home so you can move in quickly. New home warranty included along with superb customer service.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Fri, 03 Jul 2009 09:25:27 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100095</record_id><title><![CDATA[113 Loma Place, Aptos, CA]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=95]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/mdelgado/Thumbs100_Front Yard.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[113 Loma Place]]></address><city><![CDATA[Aptos]]></city><state><![CDATA[CA]]></state><zip><![CDATA[95003]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[2358]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[3684]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2009</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>1275000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Laundry area - garage, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Microwave, Yard, Granite countertop, Living room, Stainless steel appliances, Bonus/Rec room, Attic]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[2,358 Total Square Foot Complete New Build. Spanish Mexican Hacienda Beach Home, Architecturally Unique Design. Custom Beach home
Aptos California Seacliff State Park Beach Area. Location! Location! Location! Open Entertaining Floor Plan. Fifth House from Seacliff State Park Beach. Capitola, Margaritaville 15 Minute drive, Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk 20 minute drive, Monterey little over 1/2 hour away.

Tank-Less Instant Water Heater, Gas Stove with Auto Back Draft. Energy Efficient Dish Washer, Oven, Washer/Dryer & Refrigerator. Average PG&E Bill $70.00. 7 Layer Insulation, Tile Roof, Double Pane Windows, Solid Wood Perimeter & Interior Doors.  Cherry Wood Floors, Custom Wood Burning Fireplace With Electrical Blower Control Switch. Water Flow Fire Sprinkler System along with Landscape Sprinkler Drip System.  Stucco Exterior through out, Bull Nose Interior Edges, With Plaster Interior Walls. Custom Finished Garage with Operable Window. Granite Counter Tops, Maple Custom Kitchen Cabinets, Stainless Steel Appliances, Walk-in Pantry With Large Storage. Indoor Laundry Room, Plumbed For Sink, Custom Locksets and Custom Light Fixtures. Recessed Lighting, Travertine Tile, And Three Custom Bathrooms With Unique Tile Vanities and With Hand Painted Sinks. Private Courtyard Covered Veranda, Covered Balcony and Sun Deck Balcony. Interior Curved Stairway, Exterior Courtyard Stairwell. Open Loft To Living Room (with 16’ Ceiling/cathedral windows) Detached 11x12 Room/Storage. Blue Prints Can Be Available]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Jul 2009 21:26:20 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100101</record_id><title><![CDATA[20307 FM 685, Pflugerville, TX]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=101]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Lot/Land]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/debbie.marett/Thumbs100_pf 29 rowe.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[20307 FM 685]]></address><city><![CDATA[Pflugerville]]></city><state><![CDATA[TX]]></state><zip><![CDATA[78660]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>4</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1818]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[5.04 acres]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1984</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>1300000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Central heat, Dining room, Laundry area - inside, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Have your home or office at your place of business !! 

2 miles from city limits 

Drive way located off of the feeder road at Hwy 685 and 130 toll road in Pflugerville, Texas, Travis County. ( Easy toll access ) 

417 ft front/526.55 ft deep NO RESTRICTIONS, READY TO RE-ZONE COMMERCIAL: Office/Retail/Industrial. 

This 1984, well-kept, clean, one story, 4 bedroom, 2 bath home, sits high up on a hill looking down over 5.04 acres. Home could be residence or office on commercial business property!! 

PROPERTY FEATURES: 
Bedrooms: 4 
Subdivision: Casner J - Pflugerville acres 
Full Baths: 2 
Year Built: 1984 
HOA: N/A 
Lot Size: 5.04 acres 
Parking: 2 Cars 
Sqft: 1818 
Floors: 1 

Central A/C Central heat, High/Vaulted ceiling, Family room, Living room, Dining room ,Breakfast nook, Laundry area - inside 
Improvements - see agent , Key with agent 

MAKE AN OFFER _ MOTIVATED SELLER]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 20 Jul 2009 22:01:50 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100107</record_id><title><![CDATA[12503 Issaquah Hobart Road, Issaquah, Washington]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=107]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/lizcares/Thumbs100_ISSAQUAH CREEKSIDE.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[12503 Issaquah Hobart Road]]></address><city><![CDATA[Issaquah]]></city><state><![CDATA[Washington]]></state><zip><![CDATA[98027]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>4</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[2760]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[.74]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1970</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>549950</price><amenities><![CDATA[Basement, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Microwave, Yard, Family room, Granite countertop, Living room, Attic]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[81' Waterfront-Issaquah Creek! Enjoy this beautiful home on 3/4acre! Fruit trees, roses, raspberries, blackberries, grapes, cherries... See the beauty of the NW through the wall of windows upstairs & down - looking out on the creek & mountain hillside. This home's been remodeled with pergo floors, new carpeting, updated kitchen w/corian counters, newer appliances,double pane windows & new trek deck. A Secret Room! Possible MIL downstairs! Lg shop w/extra 1car garage! This home is a must see!]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Thu, 23 Jul 2009 12:56:28 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100149</record_id><title><![CDATA[7924  Austin Ave NW, Albuquerque, NM]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=149]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/Jade_Southwest/Thumbs100_660231.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[7924  Austin Ave NW]]></address><city><![CDATA[Albuquerque]]></city><state><![CDATA[NM]]></state><zip><![CDATA[87120]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1800]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[.167]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2005</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>179900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Yard]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Wed, 02 Sep 2009 00:24:46 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100157</record_id><title><![CDATA[2nd Ave, Conshohocken, PA]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=157]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/brenden.schultz/Thumbs100_Jesse Prom, ROB&Rich, New 143w 079.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[2nd Ave]]></address><city><![CDATA[Conshohocken]]></city><state><![CDATA[PA]]></state><zip><![CDATA[19428]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>4</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[3200]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[3+]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[5000]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built /><currency>USD</currency><price>444900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Basement, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Microwave, Yard, Granite countertop, Living room, Stainless steel appliances, Jacuzzi/Whirlpool, Bonus/Rec room, Attic]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[New Semi-Custom Twin in the heart of Conshohocken. Featuring Dual zone heat and air(Save on ur gas and elec bill), 9ft ceilings, Hardwood floors, crown molding, powder room, and a gas fireplace on the first floor. Along with Granite counter tops, tile floor, and stainless steel appliances in the kitchen. The second floor features 2 bedrooms and 2 baths and laundry.The master bath will have a Oversized stand up shower all tile with tile floors thru out bathroom.The third floor will feature 2 additional bedrooms with jack and jill bathroom.The basement has 9ft ceilings with a second half bath. The backyard will have a deck coming off the kitchen and a oversized one car garage. This beautiful twin comes move in ready with everything done with meticulous craftsmanship.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Tue, 15 Sep 2009 11:11:08 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100160</record_id><title><![CDATA[1200 Salt Marsh, Orange Park, FL]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=160]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/msklcollier/Thumbs100_058.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[1200 Salt Marsh]]></address><city><![CDATA[Orange Park]]></city><state><![CDATA[FL]]></state><zip><![CDATA[32003]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>6</bedrooms><bathrooms>5</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[4803]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[1]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2005</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>1400000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Yard, Family room, Granite countertop, Swimming pool, Living room, Stainless steel appliances, Bonus/Rec room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Enjoy This Magnificent Lakefront Home Located in Prestigious Eagle Harbor.  Take A Stroll Down Your 400ft Dock Accessing The LLOC Waterway.  Relax In The Luxurious Screened Salt Water Pool  Accessible From The Family Room Or The Owner's Suite. Entertain In Your Gourmet Kitchen Complete With Gas Cook Top, Double Ovens, Expansive Island & Breakfast Bar. Open Kitchens Overlook The Family Room /Informal Dining Room. The Formal Living/Dining/Gathering Room Is A Host's Dream, Simply Perfect for Entertaining.  The Spacious Master Suite Features Sitting Area with Built-in Bookshelves as well as a Beautiful Sprawling Bath. Work or Play in the Executive Office with Custom Built-Ins. This Home Has Two Additional Bedrooms W/ Jack & Jill Bath On Lower Level As Well As Two Bedrooms W/ Jack & Jill Bath Upstairs. Bonus Room W/ Full Bath and Walk-In Closet Can Be Used As Theater Room/Recreational Room/ or Additional Bedroom. $10,000 Bonuses to Selling Agent!!!!!]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Tue, 06 Oct 2009 11:26:13 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100176</record_id><title><![CDATA[14615 Vaughan Dr, Charlotte, NC]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=176]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/kirztn/Thumbs100_2404 front.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[14615 Vaughan Dr]]></address><city><![CDATA[Charlotte]]></city><state><![CDATA[NC]]></state><zip><![CDATA[28273]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>5</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[2404]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[8004]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2008</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>209900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Microwave, Yard, Family room, Granite countertop, Swimming pool, Stainless steel appliances]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[NEW PRICE!!!! This spacious master up home in the Kingsbridge subdivision features 5 bedrooms,3.5 baths, a 2 story foyer, den and dining room. Granite counter tops, harwood flooring and stainless steel aplliances complete this lovely kitchen. Formal dining room has crown molding, chair railing and picture molding. Granite counter tops in all full baths. Open kitchen overlooks nook and family room. Fireplace with granite surround in family room. Hardwoods in foyer, hall, powder room, kitchen, breakfast nook and family room. Covered front porch to enjoy. Home is on a wooded lot!]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Fri, 30 Oct 2009 15:54:51 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100201</record_id><title><![CDATA[9908 Thistle Field Ln, Charlotte, NC]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=201]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/adamshomescharlotte/Thumbs100_lot 112 front.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[9908 Thistle Field Ln]]></address><city><![CDATA[Charlotte]]></city><state><![CDATA[NC]]></state><zip><![CDATA[28273]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>5</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[3821]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[.34]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2009</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>259305</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Microwave, Yard, Family room, Granite countertop, Living room, Stainless steel appliances, Bonus/Rec room, Attic]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[This gorgeous 3821 sf master down home features 5 spacious bedrooms, 3.5 baths, both formal rooms and a giant bonus room. It's dramatic 2 story foyer overlooks front entrance. Crown molding, picture molding and chair railing in formal dining room. Beautiful hardwoods throughout the foyer, hall, powder room, kitchen and breakfast nook. Granite counter tops in kitchen and all 3 full baths. Open kitchen overlooks breakfast nook and family room. Huge laundry room on 1st floor. Fireplace with granite surround in family room. Covered front porch to enjoy. Home sits on a 1/3 of an acre cul-de-sac lot.  This home is in the desirable Kingsbridge subdivision. The community features a swimming pool, tot pool, cabana, changing rooms and bathrooms, wooded common area, sidewalks and old fashion street lamp posts throughout neighborhood.

The Kingsbridge community is in an absolute great location! It is close to I-77 and I-485 exchange for an easy commute to surrounding towns. It is just minutes away from shopping, dining and entertainment. Equal Housing opportunity.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Wed, 06 Jan 2010 14:59:45 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100206</record_id><title><![CDATA[753 Casper Dr, Lafayette, CO]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=206]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Townhouse]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/images/NoimageHome.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[753 Casper Dr]]></address><city><![CDATA[Lafayette]]></city><state><![CDATA[CO]]></state><zip><![CDATA[80026]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>2</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1205]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[3+]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[1494]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2005</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>215000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Refrigerator, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Microwave, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Enjoy this cozy, charming town home in peaceful, quiet Coal Creek Village. The laminate wood floors & open floor plan are enhanced by the streams of sunlight. The kitchen has cherry cabinets w/crown molding, dbl stainless sink and loads of countertop space, The balcony is great for gardening veggies and flowers in pots and there is still plenty of room for a grill. Tankless hot water heater, Laundry room and coat closet on the 1st floor are next to your private secure garage. NOT short sale.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Sun, 24 Jan 2010 20:32:12 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100218</record_id><title><![CDATA[83125 N Shore Dr, Indio, California]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=218]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Lot/Land]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/amysims/Thumbs100_shadow lake.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[83125 N Shore Dr]]></address><city><![CDATA[Indio]]></city><state><![CDATA[California]]></state><zip><![CDATA[92202]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>0</bedrooms><bathrooms>1</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[30,056]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2003</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>595000</price><amenities><![CDATA[]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[DISCOVER THE DESERTS SECRET OASIS! SHADOW LAKE ESTATES READY FOR CUSTOM BUILT HOMES. DESIREABLE FOR WATER SKIERS, WAKE BOARDERS, FISHING AND RELAXING. MULTI-MILLION DOLLAR HOMES ALREADY BUILT. ENJOY THIS LUXURIOUS CELEBRITY LIFESTYLE LAKE FRONT VERY FEW CUSTOM HOMES TO BE BUILT.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Tue, 09 Feb 2010 21:03:39 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100227</record_id><title><![CDATA[6060 Whetstone Dr, Colorado Springs, CO]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=227]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/sandra/Thumbs100_DSCN0118.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[6060 Whetstone Dr]]></address><city><![CDATA[Colorado Springs]]></city><state><![CDATA[CO]]></state><zip><![CDATA[80923]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>5</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[3306]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[6969]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1998</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>264900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Office/Den, Basement, Central heat, Dishwasher, Walk-in closet, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Tile floor, Microwave, Yard, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Gogeous 5 bed 4 bath home with all neutral color paint and carpet. This property has just been completely remodeled and is ready to move in. Close to school, shopping and hospital.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Thu, 18 Feb 2010 09:52:13 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100228</record_id><title><![CDATA[153 Cherry Cir, Fountain, CO]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=228]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/sandra/Thumbs100_P7170003.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[153 Cherry Cir]]></address><city><![CDATA[Fountain]]></city><state><![CDATA[CO]]></state><zip><![CDATA[80817]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>1</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1536]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[0.14]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1971</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>134900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Office/Den, Central heat, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Gorgeous 3 bedroom home,rcently remodeled. New vinyl windows. Neutral color paint and carptet. Landscaped front. Large Deck, new driveway. The list goes on and on. Walking distance from school and only minutes from shopping and I25]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Fri, 19 Feb 2010 09:31:50 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100235</record_id><title><![CDATA[1265 Millbrook Cir, Bradenton, FL]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=235]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/tmurphy52/Thumbs100_P1030632.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[1265 Millbrook Cir]]></address><city><![CDATA[Bradenton]]></city><state><![CDATA[FL]]></state><zip><![CDATA[34212]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1602]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[5183]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2001</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>172500</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Microwave, Yard, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Extremely Well Cared for 3Br/2Ba Home In A Maintenance-Free Golfing Community. Not A Short Sale! Take A Short Walk To The Clubhouse For 18 Holes, Or Enjoy The Sun At The Nearby Heated Community Pool. This Home Features A Combination Living/Dining Room, Family Room, And Well-Equipped Kitchen With Newer Refrigerator And Gas Appliances. The Extended Lanai Has Ceramic Tile And Offers Lots Of Covered Outdoor Space. The Backyard Is Nicely Landscaped And Fenced For Total Privacy, And The Garage Is Equipped With Overhead Cabinets For Additional Storage.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Thu, 04 Mar 2010 14:04:27 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100241</record_id><title><![CDATA[2408 Bayshore Gardens Pkwy, Bradenton, FL]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=241]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/tmurphy52/Thumbs100_P1030035.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[2408 Bayshore Gardens Pkwy]]></address><city><![CDATA[Bradenton]]></city><state><![CDATA[FL]]></state><zip><![CDATA[34207]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>1</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1108]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[7562]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1959</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>79999</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Tile floor, Microwave, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Escape the winter snows in this adorable bungalow!  Wonderful community offers boat slips for only a few dollars a day with direct access to the Gulf of Mexico, an olympic sized pool for soaking up the sun, and an active community center and park.  If you've been looking for an affordable Florida get-away.... you've found it!  Check out the low cost of ownership - only $320 per year for HOA fees.  The home features ceramic tile throughout all living areas and carpet in the bedrooms.  Oversized backyard can be inexpensively landscapped for additional privacy and plenty of room to add a pool.  Also available furnished for $99,999.  MOTIVATED SELLER - ALL REASONABLE OFFERS CONSIDERED - UP TO 20% OWNER FINANCING AVAILABLE.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 08 Mar 2010 11:42:47 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100242</record_id><title><![CDATA[1446 Millbrook Cir, Bradenton, FL]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=242]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/tmurphy52/Thumbs100_Exterior Front.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[1446 Millbrook Cir]]></address><city><![CDATA[Bradenton]]></city><state><![CDATA[FL]]></state><zip><![CDATA[34212]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>2</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1782]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[5183]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1999</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>199000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Tile floor, Microwave, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Beautiful golf course views from your lanai, community maintained lawns and low HOA fees.  Community pool to enjoy close by.  2 car garage, security system, and a oversized screened lanai. Centrally located with easy access to the beaches and 45 minutes to Tampa International Airport.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 08 Mar 2010 12:10:57 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100243</record_id><title><![CDATA[3101 Vivienda Blvd, Bradenton, FL]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=243]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Apartment/Condo/Townhouse]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/tmurphy52/Thumbs100_Front Exterior.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[3101 Vivienda Blvd]]></address><city><![CDATA[Bradenton]]></city><state><![CDATA[FL]]></state><zip><![CDATA[34207]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>2</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1726]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[0]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1981</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>123500</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[This Villa is in a well  maintained community, located across the street from the State College of Sarasota. Separate Dining Room, large Living Room and 2 Master Suites. Beautiful Community Pool to enjoy. Year round residents and snowbirds. Sit in the Florida Room and enjoy the views.  Come have a look. Must own and be a resident  for 2 years before renting out. $100 Fee for Association Application Approval.  UP TO 20% OWNER FINANCING AVAILABLE.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 08 Mar 2010 12:45:58 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100244</record_id><title><![CDATA[318 167th Blvd. NE, Bradenton, FL]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=244]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/tmurphy52/Thumbs100_Exterior Front.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[318 167th Blvd. NE]]></address><city><![CDATA[Bradenton]]></city><state><![CDATA[FL]]></state><zip><![CDATA[34212]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>4</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[2732]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[21845]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2007</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>340000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Family room, Granite countertop, Swimming pool, Living room, Jacuzzi/Whirlpool, Bonus/Rec room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Enjoy the open spaces in this brand New, never lived in, pool home in growing Rye Wilderness.  This home features 3 bedrooms plus a bonus room that could be used as a 4th bedroom, 3 full baths, separate study, large family room, plus formal living and dining rooms.  Enjoy the beautiful Florida sunshine in the beautiful pool and spa.  The pool and lanai is open with no cage to block the view, but for those who prefer a cage, one can be easily added for less than $5,000 (ask listing agent for details).  The kitchen features  Granite countertops with tile backsplash, and solid wood cabinets.  Managing your cars and other belongings is easy with an oversized 3 car side-load garage with extra-wide driveway paved with brick paver stones.   All this on a large 1/2 acre lot.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 08 Mar 2010 12:56:04 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100245</record_id><title><![CDATA[703 65th Ave W, Bradenton, FL]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=245]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/tmurphy52/Thumbs100_P1030020.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[703 65th Ave W]]></address><city><![CDATA[Bradenton]]></city><state><![CDATA[FL]]></state><zip><![CDATA[34207]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>4</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1406]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[7000]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1970</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>139900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Central heat, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Microwave, Swimming pool, Living room, Stainless steel appliances]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[You will fall in love with this lovingly cared for and completely updated pool home. Ready for immediate closing and not a short sale. Look at these updates -new roof in 2004, new high-efficiency A/C in 2005, new kitchen with solid-surface counters, solid wood cabinets, and stainless appliances in 2006.  Large fenced backyard with a beautiful pool to entertain your friends and family. What more could you ask for!]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 08 Mar 2010 13:13:27 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100250</record_id><title><![CDATA[16416 E 119th Place #C, Commerce City, CO]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=250]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/sales/Thumbs100_16416C-email5.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[16416 E 119th Place #C]]></address><city><![CDATA[Commerce City]]></city><state><![CDATA[CO]]></state><zip><![CDATA[80022]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>4</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[3786]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[n/a]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2008</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>295671</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Basement, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Microwave, Family room, Granite countertop, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Sun, 21 Mar 2010 16:27:26 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100251</record_id><title><![CDATA[2415 Anjelina Cir. W, Colorado Springs, CO]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=251]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/sandra/Thumbs100_DSCN0192.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[2415 Anjelina Cir. W]]></address><city><![CDATA[Colorado Springs]]></city><state><![CDATA[CO]]></state><zip><![CDATA[80916]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>5</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1905]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[9600]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1972</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>164900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Basement, Central heat, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Yard, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Gorgeous home on huge corner lot. Just remodeled in all neutral colors. New kitchen with tile flooring and french doors walking out to the big yard. All new vinyl windows, carpet, paint, six panel closet doors, new garage door and the list goes on and on.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 22 Mar 2010 09:28:04 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100252</record_id><title><![CDATA[601 San Clemente, Colorado Springs, CO]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=252]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/sandra/Thumbs100__PKP7598.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[601 San Clemente]]></address><city><![CDATA[Colorado Springs]]></city><state><![CDATA[CO]]></state><zip><![CDATA[80906]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>5</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[2125]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[4356]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1972</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>184900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Basement, Central heat, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Microwave, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[FREE TRIP TO MEXICO FOR 2 ALL INCLUSIVE WITH FULL PRICE OFFER

compeltely remodeled home, offers 5 bedrooms, 3 bathrooms and an oversized 2 car garage on corner lot. The huge kitchen is a chef's delight with brand new classy merlot cabinets beautiful neutral color tile flooring, glass top stove and built in microwave. New vinyl windows throughout, neutral color paint with trim. Upgraded carpet and padding. This is a must see!!!]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 22 Mar 2010 10:44:00 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100254</record_id><title><![CDATA[2535 E. Cache la Poudre St., Colorado Springs, CO]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=254]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/sandra/Thumbs100__PKP7569.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[2535 E. Cache la Poudre St.]]></address><city><![CDATA[Colorado Springs]]></city><state><![CDATA[CO]]></state><zip><![CDATA[80909]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1752]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[9148]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1939</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>184900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Basement, Central heat, Stove/Oven, Tile floor, Microwave, Family room, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[FREE ONE WEEK TRIP TO HAWAII FOR 2 PEOPLE WITH FULL PRICE OFFER

Get 2 lots for the price of one!!! Completely remodeled rancher with cottage on 2nd lot zoned multi family.The main home offers a superb tiled kitchen with new hickory cabinets and counter tops. two bathrooms both newley tiled with all new fixtures and fittings,new carpet throughout the spacious 3 bedrooms and living room.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Tue, 23 Mar 2010 00:06:27 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100257</record_id><title><![CDATA[6159 harbour town ct, Orlando, FL]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=257]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Lot/Land]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/david/Thumbs100_6159 harbor town dr maher 016.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[6159 harbour town ct]]></address><city><![CDATA[Orlando]]></city><state><![CDATA[FL]]></state><zip><![CDATA[32819]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>0</bedrooms><bathrooms>1</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[29494]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built /><currency>USD</currency><price>475000</price><amenities><![CDATA[]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[This rare World Class Bay Hill golf front lot is rare indeed. The vacant lot is adjacent to the green on hole #11, overlooking the lake and golf course. The lot features west to northwest views of the golf course. You can imagine buliding your estate home with wonderful views from your second floor balcony overlooking the lake and golf course. The market area features world class dining nearby, along with shopping, business and A+ rated schools. The Orlando International airport is only minutes away. The area theme parks include Walt Disney World, Universal Studios, and Sea World. Owner will consider trade.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:33:24 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100260</record_id><title><![CDATA[3037 127th Pl SE #H-22, Bellevue, WA]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/OnlineWebPost.aspx?PWID=260]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Townhouse]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/lindyhisatomi/Thumbs100_wong back.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[3037 127th Pl SE #H-22]]></address><city><![CDATA[Bellevue]]></city><state><![CDATA[WA]]></state><zip><![CDATA[98004]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>2</bedrooms><bathrooms>1</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1040]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[2.5]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1979</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>225000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central heat, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Microwave]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Fresh & move-in ready!! Great Room w/cherry floors, cozy fireplace, built-in buffett & spacious Kitchen w/loads of counters & cabinets! Upper 2 Bedrooms feature Vaulted Ceilings & walls of Closets!  Famous Bellevue Schools!]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Wed, 21 Apr 2010 15:36:24 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100261</record_id><title><![CDATA[346 Leafmore Dr, charlotte, NC]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=261]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/stu/Thumbs100_102_0111.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[346 Leafmore Dr]]></address><city><![CDATA[charlotte]]></city><state><![CDATA[NC]]></state><zip><![CDATA[28213]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>3</bedrooms><bathrooms>1</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1000]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[.30]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1963</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>92900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Central heat, Dining room, Laundry area - inside, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Yard, Granite countertop, Living room, Stainless steel appliances, Attic]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Very nice house remodeled from the ground up, new 30 year roof, granite counters with a large back yard, many large trees, fenced with a storage shed. This is a house charlotte neighborhood so they will give you 7-10k downpayment if buy and live here for 4 years. Police get 15k!]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Thu, 22 Apr 2010 08:40:27 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100267</record_id><title><![CDATA[1213 Bentley Park, Knoxville, TN]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=267]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/jenny.snodgrass/Thumbs100_Bentely Park front (Medium).jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[1213 Bentley Park]]></address><city><![CDATA[Knoxville]]></city><state><![CDATA[TN]]></state><zip><![CDATA[37922]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>5</bedrooms><bathrooms>4</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[3537]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[3+]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[12330]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2006</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>409900</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Microwave, Yard, Family room, Granite countertop, Living room, Stainless steel appliances, Jacuzzi/Whirlpool, Bonus/Rec room, Attic]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Best deal in Bentley Park and only 1 mile from Concord Park and Marina. You will love this classic home with hardwoods on the main and staircase. Lovely kitchen with stainless steel appliances, quartz counter tops and built-in desk. Large deck open to private back yard. Upstairs you will enjoy 4 large bedrooms and 3 full baths and 745 sq. ft. finished on the 3rd level with its own full bath. A great home at a great price.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 26 Apr 2010 14:36:59 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100268</record_id><title><![CDATA[14 Darien Ct, Montgomery, TX]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=268]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Single-Family Home]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/anthony/Thumbs100_100_0276.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[14 Darien Ct]]></address><city><![CDATA[Montgomery]]></city><state><![CDATA[TX]]></state><zip><![CDATA[77356]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>4</bedrooms><bathrooms>3</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[4000]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[11554]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1999</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>460000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Tile floor, Microwave, Yard, Family room, Granite countertop, Living room, Bonus/Rec room, Attic]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Tue, 27 Apr 2010 14:02:23 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100278</record_id><title><![CDATA[505 Whitehall St.  sw, Atlanta, Georgia]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=278]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Loft]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/sillimanj/Thumbs100_271.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[505 Whitehall St.  sw]]></address><city><![CDATA[Atlanta]]></city><state><![CDATA[Georgia]]></state><zip><![CDATA[30303]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>2</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1826]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[0]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1920</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>279000</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Central heat, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Microwave, Living room, Stainless steel appliances]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Looking for an upscale industrial style loft . . . this is it.  Large sq. footage, huge bank of windows, tons of light, pvt rooftop deck, city views, . . . what more are you looking for?  This is very cool space . . . especially at this low sq. foot pricing.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Thu, 20 May 2010 15:16:02 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100279</record_id><title><![CDATA[1304 Westchester Ridge NE, Atlanta, Georgia]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=279]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Condo]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/sillimanj/Thumbs100_PoolArea.jpg]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[1304 Westchester Ridge NE]]></address><city><![CDATA[Atlanta]]></city><state><![CDATA[Georgia]]></state><zip><![CDATA[30329]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>2</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[1]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[0]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>2002</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>1300</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Microwave, Living room]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[Very nice condo for lease in gorgeous communitee.  Condo has virtually no wear & tear - lives like brand new.  Two (2) assigned, covered, and secured parking.  Split bed+bath plan - perfect for roommate or office.  Easy access & centrally located to all Atlanta has to offer.  Call for viewing:  Jay Silliman (404) 558-9854]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 24 May 2010 11:10:06 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing><listing><record_id>100280</record_id><title><![CDATA[505 Whitehall St.  SW, Atlanta, Georgia]]></title><url><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/Singlewebposts.aspx?PWID=280]]></url><category>real estate</category><subcategory><![CDATA[Loft]]></subcategory><image><PictureUrl><![CDATA[http://webposts.flyerme.com/SlideShow/sillimanj/Thumbs100_271.JPG]]></PictureUrl><Caption /></image><address><![CDATA[505 Whitehall St.  SW]]></address><city><![CDATA[Atlanta]]></city><state><![CDATA[Georgia]]></state><zip><![CDATA[30303]]></zip><country>United States</country><bedrooms>2</bedrooms><bathrooms>2</bathrooms><square_footage><![CDATA[1800]]></square_footage><stories><![CDATA[2]]></stories><lot_size><![CDATA[1800]]></lot_size><parking_spots><![CDATA[1]]></parking_spots><year_built>1920</year_built><currency>USD</currency><price>1800</price><amenities><![CDATA[Central A/C, Office/Den, Central heat, Dining room, Dishwasher, Laundry area - inside, Walk-in closet, Refrigerator, Hardwood floor, Stove/Oven, Balcony, Deck, or Patio, Microwave, Living room, Stainless steel appliances]]></amenities><description><![CDATA[FULLY FURNISHED authentic loft for lease.  2 bed x 2 bath on seperate floors for roommate privacy or perfect for home office.  In building parking.  And the views from the private rooftop deck . . . the best.  Call me for a showing.  Jay Silliman  404-558-9854.]]></description><listing_time><![CDATA[Mon, 24 May 2010 12:20:55 GMT]]></listing_time><expire_time /></listing></listings>